{
  "activeEventId": "london2023",
  "admins": {
    "57MrWonzPRNLuDlAw3GHPJ81H4M2": "Todd",
    "6fgpAQCVh0XnENhSWeILL0oPWQy1": "Martine"
  },
  "answers": {},
  "questions": {
    "q00": {
      "questionText": "\"ðŸ’©\" - \"ðŸ’©\"",
      "answer": "NaN",
      "used": false
    },
    "q01": {
      "questionText": "\"ðŸ’©\".length",
      "answer": "2",
      "used": false
    },
    "q02": {
      "questionText": "0.1 + 0.2",
      "answer": "0.30000000000000004",
      "used": false
    },
    "q03": {
      "questionText": "[1, 2, 3] + [4, 5, 6]",
      "answer": "1,2,34,5,6",
      "used": false
    },
    "q04": {
      "questionText": "1 / 0",
      "answer": "Infinity",
      "used": false
    },
    "q05": {
      "questionText": "+\"42\"",
      "answer": "42",
      "used": false
    },
    "q06": {
      "questionText": "[10, 5, 1].sort()",
      "answer": "[1, 10, 5]",
      "used": false
    },
    "q07": {
      "questionText": "NaN == NaN",
      "answer": "false",
      "used": false
    },
    "q08": {
      "questionText": "3 > 2 > 1",
      "answer": "false",
      "used": false
    },
    "q09": {
      "questionText": "typeof typeof 1",
      "answer": "string",
      "used": false
    },
    "q10": {
      "questionText": "typeof null",
      "answer": "\"object\"",
      "used": false
    },
    "q11": {
      "questionText": "null instanceof Object",
      "answer": "false",
      "used": false
    },
    "q12": {
      "questionText": "return\n  { id: 42 };",
      "answer": "undefined",
      "used": false
    },
    "q13": {
      "questionText": "[] + []",
      "answer": "\"\"",
      "used": false
    },
    "q14": {
      "questionText": "(function foo(a, b) {}).length",
      "answer": "2",
      "used": false
    },
    "q15": {
      "questionText": "(\"js\", \"rocks\")",
      "answer": "\"rocks\"",
      "used": false
    },
    "q16": {
      "questionText": "!!~[1, 2, 3].indexOf(3)",
      "answer": "true",
      "used": false
    },
    "q17": {
      "questionText": "Array(0, 1, Array(2))",
      "answer": "[0, 1, [undefined, undefined]]",
      "used": false
    }
  }
}